const quizQuestions = [
    {
    question: "What is Comic Book Guy's real name?",
    answers: {
        a: "Clark Thompson", 
        b: "Herschel Krustowsky", 
        c: "Jeffrey Albertson", 
        d: "Tom McNeil"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
    question:"What was the name of Grampa's military unit in World War 2?",
    answers: {
        a: "The Flying Hellfish", 
        b: "The Savage Shellfish", 
        c: "The Tussle Tanks", 
        d: "The Subpar Subbers"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a",
    },
    {
    question: "What is the password Mr Burns uses to enter his panic room? (hint, it's also his place of birth!)",
    answers: {
        a: "Nantucket", 
        b: "Shelbyville", 
        c: "Pangea", 
        d: "Ogdenville"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c",
    },
    {
    question: "What is the Crazy Cat Lady's real name?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Susan Diamond", 
        b: "Francine Cauldron", 
        c: "Gertrude Fronch", 
        d: "Eleanor Abernathy"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
    question: "What is Groundskeeper Willies Surname?",
    answers: { 
        a: "McArthur", 
        b: "MacDonald", 
        c: "McKenzie", 
        d: "MacDougal"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d",
    },
    {
    question: "What is the name of the University Moe attended?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Drinkston University", 
        b: "Swigmore University", 
        c: "Chugsville University", 
        d: "He didn't attend University"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b",
    },
    {
    question: "What is the pet name of the car driven by the bandit Snake?",
    answers: {
         a: "Red Rooster", 
         b: "King Cobra", 
         c: "Canyonero", 
         d: "Lil' Bandit"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
    question: "What job does Krusty the Clowns dad have?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Carpenter", 
        b: "Rabbi", 
        c: "Organ shop owner", 
        d: "Car salesman"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
    question: "Who is the head of the Springfield Historical Society?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Hollis Hurlbut", 
        b: "Colin Chowder", 
        c: "Professor Frink", 
        d: "Chester Springfield"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
    question: "What was the brand of TV Homer had when he was a child?",
    answers: { 
        a: "The Panaphonic", 
        b: "Carnivale", 
        c: "The Radiation King", 
        d: "Magnetbox"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
    question: "What is the name of the therapist Marge sees to help with her fear of flying?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Lowenstein", 
        b: "Bancroft", 
        c: "Zweig", 
        d: "Lionheart"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
    question: "What job did Ned Flanders have before he owned the Leftorium?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Gardener", 
        b: "Barber", 
        c: "Pharmaceutical Representative", 
        d: "Church organist"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
    question: "How did Poochie die?",
    answers: { 
        a: "He accidently ate chocolate", 
        b: "Itchy and Scratchy disembowled him", 
        c: " He was ran over by a steamroller", 
        d: "He died on the way back to his home planet"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
    question: "What was the name of the internet company that Homer set up?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Compu-Global-Hyper-Mega-Net", 
        b: "Homer's Interwebs Service", 
        c: "Simpson's Slimline Internet Services", 
        d: "Micro-Worldwide-Super-Massive-Web"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
    question: "Bart has a middle name beginning with J, what is it?",
    answers: { 
        a: "Jay", 
        b: "Juju", 
        c: "Jojo", 
        d:"Jebediah"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
    }
];